

110C Imperial Avenue
Westport, Connecticut, 06880
grahamzemel126@gmail.com
Website: https://grahamzemel.xyz
LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/gzemel
Github: https://qithub.com/gzemel

Experienced developer with a background in computer science and 5+ years experience in both technical support, web SEO, sales, and cybersecurity. Seeking to gain software engineering experience or web app development skills. An avid bug bounty hunter and Linux enthusiast.

# **Professional Experience**

### Full Stack Developer

Bratskeir Electronics LLC | April 2022 - Present

Norwalk, CT

### **Account Executive**

We Recycle Computers | May 2022 - Present

Norwalk, CT

# **Education**

# **GED** in Computer Science

Staples High School at Westport, CT | August 2020 - Present

3.65 GPA, president of 3 computer science-related clubs, completing all 8 computer courses that Staples High School offers. Completed 3 courses as of sophomore year, including AP Computer Science Principles, and passed the exam.

# Web Application Security Internet Security E-commerce Web Application Development Data Entry E-Commerce Web Development Sales Computer Forensics Networking Pen-Testing Tools

# **Accomplishments**

### App Published

Created and published The Vault Collection using Unity, published on the Apple App Store and Google Play. Roughly a 3 month project.

Java, Javascript, Python

# Cybersecurity Expertise

Working for 2-4 hours per day for many weeks at a time. Achievements include creating a wifi replication hack and deauthentication script with an ESP8266 chip, creating custom trojans in python, ruby, and shellcodes, and working with Kali Linux and virtualization to create multiple virtual hacking machines.

# Programming Expertise

Spending 1-3 hours per day when not working on cybersecurity projects. Creating new programs, games, and apps using C#, python, and Javascript. Also using a bit of HTML5, ruby, shellcode, and CSS3.

## **Extracurriculars**

President of the Coding Club at Staples High School
President of the Cryptocurrency Club at Staples High School
President of the Cybersecurity Club at Staples High School
Intro to Cybersecurity Online Course